<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugoio on Operational Dev</title>
    <link>https://operationaldev.com/tags/hugoio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugoio on Operational Dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>operationaldev@gmail.com (Automationeering)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>operationaldev@gmail.com (Automationeering)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 09:00:17 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://operationaldev.com/tags/hugoio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting Operational Dev.com - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://operationaldev.com/post/hosting-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 09:00:17 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>operationaldev@gmail.com (Automationeering)</author>
      <guid>https://operationaldev.com/post/hosting-part1/</guid>
      <description>Right before we setup any hosting, we actually need something to host right? Previously I had used wordpress, but it&amp;rsquo;s a bit complex and has way more functionality than I need. Enter Hugo. Hugo is a open source framework for generating websites. It&amp;rsquo;s really easy to use and it makes the automation part of building and deploying a blog really easy.
There are a few different options for installing (see https://gohugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How we build and host Operational Dev</title>
      <link>https://operationaldev.com/post/hosting-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 16:00:17 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>operationaldev@gmail.com (Automationeering)</author>
      <guid>https://operationaldev.com/post/hosting-overview/</guid>
      <description>I figured the best topic to start with would be how we automatically build and deploy the Operationaldev.com blog. As the blog is all automation, surely we don&amp;rsquo;t build it using handraulics.
To build our blog, we use the following components:
 vim - editing content (Ed: If you saw bob use vim, you would recommend he does not use vim) Hugo - framework for building websites AWS - our hosting provider Terraform - automate the build of all the components used to host this site Travis CI - CI tool we use to automatically push changes Github - source control  Over the next four posts we will cover in detail how we use each of these tools to bring you this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>